{
    "id": "0b7e8b95fcee47ce92be510a423bbb47",
    "title": "Sentence Completion",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "After the visitors ……………. I went into my room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "went",
                "gone",
                "had gone",
                "have gone"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The accused ………………….. by the police.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "interrogated",
                "were interrogating",
                "being interrogated",
                "were being interrogated"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "No one ……………….. a fraudster.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "likes",
                "is liking",
                "liked"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We ………………… our country.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shall not betray",
                "shall not betrayed",
                "do not shall betray"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………….. your letter yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "received",
                "was received",
                "had received",
                "would receive"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It takes two ——— a quarrel.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to making",
                "to make",
                "to made",
                "made"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The thief ………………… red-handed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "caught",
                "was caught",
                "has caught",
                "would catch"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The Delhi-Mumbai flight ……………….. by two hours due to a bomb scare.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "delayed",
                "has delayed",
                "was delayed",
                "had delayed"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The stadium …………………. with dance and music as artists from various parts of the world ......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "reverberate, performed",
                "reverberated, performed",
                "was reverberated, performed",
                "reverberated, was performed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………….. animals, but he also ……………….. many man eaters.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "love, kill",
                "loved, killed",
                "was loved, was killed",
                "had loved, had killed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}